<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Diva</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dwelcome"><b>Welcome to DIVA!</b></string>
    <string name="dintro">DIVA (Damn insecure and vulnerable App) is an App intentionally
                          designed to be insecure. The aim of the App is to teach
                          developers/QA/security professionals, flaws that are
                          generally present in the Apps due poor or insecure coding
                          practices. If you are reading this you want to either learn
                          App pentesting or secure coding and I sincerely hope that
                          DIVA solves your purpose. So, sit back and enjoy the ride.</string>
    <string name="chk_pin">check_pin</string>
    <string name="d1">1. Insecure Logging</string>
    <string name="d2">2. Hardcoding Issues - Part 1</string>
    <string name="d3">3. Insecure Data Storage - Part 1</string>
    <string name="d4">4. Insecure Data Storage - Part 2</string>
    <string name="d5">5. Insecure Data Storage - Part 3</string>
    <string name="d6">6. Insecure Data Storage - Part 4</string>
    <string name="d7">7. Input Validation Issues - Part 1</string>
    <string name="d8">8. Input Validation Issues - Part 2</string>
    <string name="d9">9. Access Control Issues - Part 1</string>
    <string name="d10">10. Access Control Issues - Part 2</string>
    <string name="d11">11. Access Control Issues - Part 3</string>
    <string name="d12">12. Hardcoding Issues - Part 2</string>
    <string name="d13">13. Input Validation Issues - Part 3</string>
    <string name="log_intro"><b>Objective</b>: Find out what is being logged where/how and the vulnerable code.\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Insecure logging occurs when developers intentionally
                             or unintentionally log sensitive information such as
                             credentials, session IDs, financial details etc.</string>
    <string name="log_enter">Enter your credit card number</string>
    <string name="log_checkout">Check out</string>
    <string name="hardcode_intro"><b>Objective</b>: Find out what is hardcoded a`nd where.\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Developers sometimes will hardcode sensitive information for ease.</string>
    <string name="hardcode_enter">Enter the vendor key</string>
    <string name="hardcode_access">ACCESS</string>
    <string name="ids1_intro"><b>Objective</b>: Find out where/how the credentials are being stored and the vulnerable code.\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Insecure data storage is the result of storing confidential information insecurely
                             on the system i.e. poor encryption, plain text, access control issues etc. </string>
    <string name="ids1_user">Enter 3rd party service user name</string>
    <string name="ids1_password">Enter 3rd party service password</string>
    <string name="ids1_save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="ivi1_intro"><b>Objective</b>: Try to access all user data without knowing any user name. There are three users
                             by default and your task is to output data of all the three users with a single malicious search.\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Improper or no input validation issue arise when the input is not filtered or validated
                             before using it. When developing components that take input from outside, always validate it.
                             For ease of testing there are three users already present in the database, for example one of them is
                             admin, you can try searching for admin to test the output.</string>
    <string name="ivi1_enter">Enter user name to search</string>
    <string name="ivi1_search">SEARCH</string>
    <string name="ivi2_intro"><b>Objective</b>: Try accessing any sensitive information apart from a web URL.\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Improper or no input validation issue arise when the input is not filtered or validated
                             before using it. When developing components that take input from outside, always validate it.
                             </string>
    <string name="ivi2_enter">Enter the URL to view</string>

    <string name="ivi2_view">VIEW</string>

    <string name="aci1_intro"><b>Objective</b>: You are able to access the API credentials when you click the button. Now, try to access the API credentials from outside the app.\n
                              <b>Hint:</b>Components of an app can be accessed from other apps or users if they are not
                              properly protected. Components such as activities, services, content providers are prone to this.</string>
    <string name="aci1_view">VIEW API CREDENTIALS</string>
    <string name="apic_label">Vendor API Credentials</string>

    <string name="aci2_intro"><b>Objective</b>: You are able to access the Third Party app TVEETER API credentials after you
                              have registered with Tveeter.
                              The App requests you to register online and the vendor gives you a pin, which you can use to register
                              with the app. Now, try to access the API credentials from outside the app without knowing the PIN.
                              This is a business logic problem so you may need to see the code.\n
                              <b>Hint:</b>Components of an app can be accessed from other apps or users if they are not
                              properly protected and some may also accept external inputs. Components such as activities,
                              services, content providers are prone to this.</string>
    <string name="aci2_alreadyreg">Already Registered.</string>
    <string name="aci2_regnow">Register Now.</string>
    <string name="apic2_enter">Enter PIN received from Tveeter</string>
    <string name="aci2_view">VIEW TVEETER API CREDENTIALS</string>
    <string name="apic2_label">Tveeter API Credentials</string>
    <string name="notesprovider_url">content://jakhar.aseem.diva.provider.notesprovider/notes</string>

    <string name="aci3_intro"><b>Objective</b>: This is a private notes application. You can create a PIN
                              once and access your notes after entering the correct pin. Now, try to access the private notes
                              from outside the app without knowing the PIN.\n
                              <b>Hint:</b>Components of an app can be accessed from other apps or users if they are not
                              properly protected and some may also accept external inputs. Components such as activities,
                              services, content providers are prone to this.</string>
    <string name="pkey">notespin</string>
    <string name="pnotes">Diva Private Notes</string>
    <string name="aci3_enterpin">Enter 4 Digit PIN</string>
    <string name="aci3_createpin">CREATE/CHANGE PIN</string>
    <string name="aci3_gotonotes">GO TO PRIVATE NOTES</string>
    <string name="aci3_accessnotes">ACCESS PRIVATE NOTES</string>
    <string name="ivi3_intro"><b>Objective</b>: This is a Missile Launch App. Spread love not War! DOS the Damn thing! Your
                             objective here is to NOT find the code and then launch the missiles, rather it is
                             to crash the app (and then find the root cause the crash).\n
                             <b>Hint</b>: Improper or no input validation issue arise when the input is not filtered or validated
                             before using it. When developing components that take input from outside, always validate it.
                             This is a classic memory corruption vulnerability. If you can get code execution, I would love to hear
                             from you. I dont expect anyone to go that far though.</string>
    <string name="ivi3_enter">Enter Launch Code for WOMD</string>
    <string name="ivi3_stop">PUSH THE RED BUTTON</string>
</resources>
